<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HOME</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on HOME</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khaledngm11.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Faculty write-up (HackTheBox)</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/faculty/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/faculty/</guid><description>Faculty write-up HackTheBox Link to heading 1. Port Scan Enumuration Link to heading 2. Directory Fuzzing Link to heading 3. Exploitation Link to heading 4. Privilege Escalation Link to heading USER Link to heading ROOT Link to heading Port Scan (Nmap) Link to heading First We will scan target with nmap nmap -sV -sC 10.10.11.169 I found two open ports ssh and http Starting Nmap 7.92 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2022-10-13 15:19 EDT Nmap scan report for faculty.</description></item><item><title>Digital forensics write-ups (CyberTalents)</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/digital-forensics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/digital-forensics/</guid><description>We will discuss Some of digital forensics CTFs at CyberTalents (It will be updated) Link to heading 1-G&amp;amp;P Link to heading Just Open the File and Capture the flag . Submission in MD5
First of all we have to download document file and lets use string command to check file content .
┌──(kali㉿kali)-[~/Downloads] └─$ strings G\&amp;amp;P+lists.docx | grep -E [a-f0-9]{32} Flag.txt877c1fa0445adaedc5365d9c139c5219PK As we see the submission of flag is md5 so we used -E Flag to identify the chars and length of md5 hash .</description></item><item><title>Leviathan walkthrough</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/leviathan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/leviathan/</guid><description>OverTheWire: Leviathan Walkthrough Link to heading We will discuss Leviathan game walkthrough ,This wargame doesn&amp;rsquo;t require any knowledge about programming - just a bit of common sense and some knowledge about basic *nix commands .
ssh connection level0 level1 level2 level3 level4 level5 level6 level7 ssh connection ssh user@host -p port Link to heading first we have to establish ssh connection using ssh leviathan0@leviathan.labs.overthewire.org -p 2223 and password leviathan0 level0 Link to heading then let&amp;rsquo;s use ls -la command to list files and directories.</description></item><item><title>Previse write-up (HackTheBox)</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/previse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/previse/</guid><description>Previse write-up HackTheBox Link to heading 1. Port Scan Enumuration Link to heading 2. Exploitation Link to heading 3. Privilege Escalation Link to heading USER Link to heading ROOT Link to heading Port Scan (Nmap) Link to heading First We will scan target with nmap nmap -sV -sC 10.10.11.104 I found two open ports ssh and http Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-09-02 03:00 EDT Stats: 0:02:04 elapsed; 0 hosts completed (1 up), 1 undergoing Connect Scan Connect Scan Timing: About 39.</description></item><item><title>Text Manipulation Using Linux Commands</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/text-manipulation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/posts/text-manipulation/</guid><description>Linux Text Processing Tools Link to heading grep
cut
sed
sort
uniq
tr
Examples ( most important )
Log file analysis Frequency analysis 1. grep Link to heading GREP is a tool that uses Regular Expressions, and prints any lines which match a specified pattern .
Syntax grep [options] pattern [files]
Most important Options: -c: Count the number of lines that match a pattern. -h: Display the matched lines, but do not display the filenames.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/about/</guid><description>Education and relevant courses Link to heading Graduated from Faculty of Computers and Artificial Intelligence ( Information Technology Department ) E-learn security penetration testing student .(PTS) E-learn security penetration testing professional .(PTPv5) E-learn security web application penetration testing .(WAPTv2) Linux redhat admin 1&amp;amp;2 . Network+ . Autopsy and cyber triage DFIR certified . Technical skills Link to heading Network vulnerability scan and penetration testing (plan , discover , exploit , report and remediation).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://khaledngm11.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://khaledngm11.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Follow me, @ngm_404.</description></item></channel></rss>